(Star Wars fanfare playing)
♪ ♪
Guys, tickets already went on sale!
What?!
(Howard:)They're not supposed
to be available yet.
(Leonard:)I don't know what to tell
you, but they're on sale!
What? Wait. You're sure
they're Star Wars tickets?
No, it's Steel Magnolias 2:
Even Steelier.
(Sheldon:)The Web site's frozen.
I can't get in!
LEONARD: Yeah, me, too.
WOLOWITZ: Same here!
Guys, they're gonna sell out!
What are we gonna do?!
(Sheldon:)All right, this goes
against everything I stand for,
(Sheldon:)but desperate times call
for desperate measures.
(Sheldon:)Lord...
(Sheldon:)This is Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)You're good friends with my mom.
(Sheldon:)I know I've spent my life
denying that you exist.
Got 'em!
And I will continue to do so!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪